Now, for step two of cleaning data programmatically,
现在 第二个步骤 即编程数据清理
we actually get to code.
我们现在要开始编码了
Let's convert our cleaning definitions into Python code.
我们来把清理定义转换成 Python 代码
Before we make any modifications to the dataset though,
但在我们对数据集做出修改之前
let's make a copy of it so we can access the original data set later.
我们先制作副本 这样我们稍后可以访问原始数据集
We can do this using Pandas.copy function.
我们可以利用 pandas.copy 函数来做这件事
And we'll call the data frame that is returned df_clean.
我们把返回的DataFrame称为 df_clean
It's not clean yet, but it soon will be.
虽然它还不干净 但很快就会干净的
Let's actually attack the non-descriptive column headers issue first because it's easier.
我们首先来解决非描述性列标题问题 因为这个问题更容易些
Let's switch these definitions around
我们来变换下这些定义
and we'll copy and paste the definition below the code header too.
我们也将在代码标题下方复制、粘贴该定义
This cell has to be a markdown cell to accept text.
该单元格必须成为接受文本的 markdown 单元格
Let's pull up Google and search rename columns Pandas.
我们进入 Google 然后搜索 rename columns pandas (重命名 pandas 的列)
I'm telling you, half of being a good programmer is searching skills.
要知道 搜索技能是一名优秀程序员的必备能力
The first result isn't the Pandas documentation.
第一个搜索结果不是 Pandas 文件
It's actually a stack overflow post.
它实际上是一篇关于栈溢出 (stack overflow) 的帖子
The answer here must be really helpful.
这里的回答肯定非常有帮助
Pause the video and take a second to read this question if you'd like.
如果你喜欢 请暂停视频 花点时间来阅读这个问题
Renaming columns and Pandas.
重命名列和 Pandas
I have a data table using Pandas,
我有一个使用 Pandas 的数据表
they probably mean DataFrame and column labels
它们可能是指 DataFrame 和列标签
that I need to edit to replace the original column labels.
我需要编辑 以替换原始列标签
Yeah, okay. That sounds like our issue.
是的 这听起来像我们的问题
And let's scroll down to the most up voted answer.
我们向下滚动至得票最高的回答
Here's the accepted one with the check mark, 740 up votes.
这是打了勾的热门回答 得票数为 740 票
But there's actually one down here with more, 1263.
但实际上下面还有一个得票数更多的回答 1263 票
Again, pause the video and take a second to read this answer if you'd like.
重申一下 如果你想的话 请暂停视频 花上一秒钟的时间来阅读这个回答
So, use the rename function and refer the columns to be renamed.
接着 请使用 rename 函数 指向待重命名的列
Not all the columns have to be renamed,
并非所有列都需要重命名
and it give us two options.
它给我们两个选项
So, I'll copy and paste this one here into our Jupyter Notebook.
我将把这个选项复制、粘贴至我们的 Jupyter Notebook 中
But again, you shouldn't.
但重申一下 你不该用复制粘贴的懒办法
Writing the code out will help make you a better programmer.
写出代码 将有助于使你成为一名更优秀的程序员
And we have to make this df_clean because we don't want to modify the original dataset.
而且 我们必须写出这个 df_clean 因为我们不想修改原始数据集
We want to modify the copy we just made above here.
我们想修改之前刚刚制作的副本
Okay, so the answer gave us dummy parameters.
好了 这个回答为我们给出了虚参数
{ 'oldName1' : 'NewName1',
{ 'oldName1' : 'NewName1',
'oldName2' : 'newName2' }.
'oldName2' : 'newName2' }.
In the quiz ahead,
在接下来的测试题中
replace these with our actual column headers.
用我们实际的列标题替换它们
Old and New to fix this non-descriptive and misspelled column headers issue.
即旧标题和新标题 以改正这个非描述性和拼写错误的列标题问题